relax has clear allocated your tickets in Jira yet?
okay okay okay all right
has she given, has she assigned any tickets to you?
not yet not yet for now what she told me is that tomorrow when she'll be back
we will spend some time trying to you know review a bit the
very review of the the environment and everything but
still you know as you as you you've been there for quite some time I thought to
myself maybe it is good to talk to you and and see
how things are going every day you know what are the sort of
tasks we're dealing with the the issue we have at the moment you know try to
understand a bit what is what is happening
okay I mean
I'll try for update
I'll just share my screen okay thank you so I mean honestly for the most part
like compared to other places I've worked this is like one of the most relaxed
place one of the most relaxed places so much so
that I was at rents when I started thinking you know
there was stuff that I wasn't doing that was meant to be doing yeah yeah yeah
well to be to be frank I've had the same feeling since last week to be
frank to be honest with you
honestly don't worry like we don't we don't work to
like timetables okay even even our sprints
aren't set in stone okay so our sprints are just like this is what we're going to be working on
um while we're doing it so I've basically just finished the stock db migration
okay which was literally just moving a my secret Maria db
database from a windows box on one of our Galera clusters
all right so so basically doing the tcp dump and going to to to restore that on
briefly speaking yeah I mean there is a lot of other stuff to do so there's
there's a windows server called ad center and the reason we just had to be
careful with it is because these are old old windows 2003 boxes
oh yeah so these are proper legacy and nobody touches them now
all right all right so the database itself was easy enough to migrate
um because that is just basically well I tested the applications first against
it to make sure that they behaved you know normally okay um and then it was a case
of early in the morning um
switching me i know dv tables in the read only and then dumping it and then
moving it and then changing dns so that was fairly simple
but you just need to get the biggest bit was getting the devs to sign off on it and
say yeah we're happy I haven't thought that because the devs themselves they don't
um they don't really touch it so ad center gets an update like once every six
months or so okay so again ad center is another thing
running on windows 2003 but it's just a java app so i'm currently looking at
getting that working on stage web um 01 and testing that out and then once i've
got it running i'll get it put into ansible so that we can
um deploy everywhere okay um i mean for and that's basically the only ticket i
have you can see um so i've basically got three things to do over the next
couple weeks um not including anything we've also got uh
there's a
so yeah so we've got a support chat as well yeah
so yeah i don't know if you've got all the links to it so we've got a separate um
pan ban board i guess a separate g-ra group for support requests so somebody
comes in saying something's broken or um we need this changed
and quickly so stuff that isn't like project work it's more us reacting to
something then you've got that as you can see we've got nothing in there at the
moment we don't make it one or two a week
um and one of us will pick it up or the other will pick it up and just give it
to one of us to say you know that we give it a
split and then get it done
anyway okay i mean yeah your first so your first few days
you're gonna be tribbling your thumbs quite a bit
um can't think of anything fun to do there's a bunch of videos you probably
have to watch uh like ace learning
it's like uh if you go into ace and then ace learning
and then click on another link because yeah i i did that this morning i think i
saw that this morning yeah for uh yeah yeah yeah i saw that this morning yeah
yeah so i've probably i've got lens i don't know for true but
i mean again nobody really yeah that's a bad thing to stop
but it's something you know for you to do
all right okay okay i saw that this morning so i'll
keep that in mind too too too okay all right okay and and and and and one quick
question uh sorry so in terms of the uh so beyond the the project uh the
project work uh i mean first of all the the the the
database migration you you told me about just just now
um is there a place where um the the related application is
documented or something um no i don't think so
i think for like the ad center um stuff
was that
where builder i think there might be a little read me's um
yes they might have a little read me so on um on my individual repos all right
okay but there's nothing i mean we don't deal with the
applications so like ad center it's controlled by the web team
all right they manage it so we need to just look after the infrastructure for
it so we don't really have to worry um too much about the workings of it as long
as it is working all right okay okay so so in this case then for you it
was literally literally a case of getting a dump of the
database and moving and moving it across all right
and and when you moved it to to to uh to to Cosmo DB you you you mentioned so on
Cosmo DB um did you have
a gallery okay yeah so we've got these um prod corp um
cdb host switch no the prod corp's gdpr stuff we have prod int db
those are like our internal database clusters yeah i think
um stock dbs now like the only real thing running on these
all right um so yeah with which they it's coming from
Maria 5.1 i think something really old
or 10.1 whoever's on windows 7203 and it's now on 106 so it's on a more
recent version um the application itself doesn't care
because it's very simple um but now yeah i'm working on getting
ad center working in Linux and um just getting everything set up trying to
get it working behind engine x as well because before it was
IIF i guess all right okay okay okay yeah i mean if we
look at everyone else like they've got um
i mean zoe mainly does um like is your stuff
okay zoe is very much um cloud based so she rarely touches anything that's on
premise all right okay um jason and i are more
working on you know the on on board the state stuff
um with you know dabbling of the cloud as well
okay the aim of the game is to win the game and we'll do everything
it's just easier to play to everyone's strengths at the moment
so okay and and and and i have the the the the uh
you might laugh at the question because uh you know i think i would have to
most likely ask this question to Claire but but taken into account the
the uh i don't know the the the project the you know the team has
and and and you know the things to come basically the the project we we need to
to work on soon and and and is there any particular area you
think uh i should maybe um focus on maybe because
we need more work done there i mean you know i know maybe this is most likely
Claire for Claire to answer this question but yeah i just wanted to have
any um dealings with event store and no no no no this is a just no no no no
no yeah so mel who left um but i guess you're replacing um she saw looked after
only events for stuff i've i've read up a bit on it and it is basically just a