[silence]
Hello, good morning, Zorin. Good morning.
How are you?
Ah, like an old man, you know.
Sleepy.
Yeah, well, it's worse than that, you know.
I think I'm really suffering from old age, you know.
I think it is a bad time.
Maybe I'm gonna talk to our managers and retire soon.
[laughs]
That would be nice, wouldn't it?
Absolutely, yeah.
You can't be that old, be yourself though.
Well, believe me, most people don't believe how old I am.
Really?
Yeah, yeah. How old do you think I am? Really?
Um, I don't know.
Maybe like 40 something.
Right.
Okay, so just say a number. Just say a number.
No, I don't know.
But I know in the UK it is a very sensitive subject,
but honestly, I'm very open-minded.
Just say a number, honestly.
Okay, I'll go middle range. I'll go 46.
Ah, no, I'm not 46. I'm 42.
[laughs]
But this is really old, you know. This is really old.
Back in the days, people used to retire at that age.
Oh yeah, like eight years.
Back in the old days.
[laughs]
For sure that's not that old.
Yeah, but it's not that young too.
[laughs]
And I'm fine with it. I'm fine with it.
Just the way you were talking there,
what you were going to be, you know, older.
Yeah, but honestly,
well, it's only when I start to talk about old age
that people start to ask themselves questions.
But frankly, you know, last time when we went to the office,
and that was my first time, someone asked me the question,
and they told me, "You look like 34, 35."
I said, "Oh Jesus, thank you very much.
I am not 35."
He said, "You can't be older than that."
I said, "I am much older than that."
He said, "Prove it." So I gave him my driving license.
So really, that must be fake. I say it's not fake, it's real.
[laughs]
To be fair, I wasn't even really guessing on the way you actually look.
I was just guessing because I know you've got like children,
so I was like, "Well, I can't be that young."
Well, some people, you wouldn't believe it,
but I sort of became grandfather, you know.
Okay, let me tell you how.
So my cousin, like my direct cousin,
the daughter of my father's sister,
literally, my cousin,
unfortunately, she passed away in 1991,
and back in the day, she had one daughter,
so we started to take care of her.
So she calls that because of the African culture,
she calls us dad, and me and my brother, she calls that dad.
Now, she's got kids, and guess how the kids are calling us?
[laughs]
You see, granddad indeed.
So I became a grandfather without even realizing it.
[laughs]
Quite a young granddad.
Yeah, yeah, quite young.
So every time I see them when they call me granddad,
people are like, "What is going on here?"
That can't be real.
Yeah, exactly.
They say, "What is going on here?
Was it 10 or something?"
Like, "No, what is going on?"
[laughs]
It's very young.
And Zoe, before we start, I have one question.
How do you manage to...
It sounds like a stupid question,
but how do you manage to remain so calm?
[laughs]
No, really, because there are a few things I find disturbingly annoying.
Honestly.
And I'm wondering how you manage to remain so calm.
Do you have special techniques or a special short of breath
that helps you?
[laughs]
You know what, I just put myself on mute
and then you can just say what you want, really.
Ah, that's your question.
I just do it out as well a lot of the time.
I can't handle a lot of it.
Wow, wow, wow.
Because I don't know how...
Okay, okay, so I'll follow your lead on that,
because sometimes I don't know.
I'm going to be very honest with you.
Sometimes I don't know.
I really don't get...
Sorry, but I know Jason is facing some challenges,
but the way he talks, including to our manager and so on,
I'm wondering how...
Sometimes I'm asking myself questions.
How do you manage to be so calm?
Like, this is amazing.
Honestly, like, wow.
Yeah, like...
He is actually all right.
I do agree, like, he doesn't talk very well,
but see, if I raise the point and have something to say,
he is quite nice to me.
[sighs]
So I find it difficult, because...
Like, yeah, he just goes...
He rants and rants and rants and rants and rants.
Only time, Jesus.
But, you know, he'll go through a phase,
and like, next week, he'll, like, not talk at all.
So, and then you'll be...
You'll have a nice few weeks,
and then you'll forget about all the crappy bits.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
He just goes through a lot of phases.
But yeah, because I find it, like,
it's kind of different for you.
Well, not just now, but because, especially him and Greg,
like, they're doing a lot of the on-prem,
like, work, and I'm really not involved in it.
So as soon as they start to talk about that,
I just literally don't even really pay attention.
You might not be quite in such a position
where you can just ignore all what they say about that stuff.
So that does make it easier for me.
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Honestly, you know, I think...
[sighs]
Well, okay, okay, I think I'll take your advice there,
you know, whenever this is happening,
I'll just have some short read and hope for the next week
to be better.
What can you do?
I don't know, like, it clear, it's quite good
at sticking out for her as well, so...
No!
Sometimes she'll just take it,
and then sometimes she will pick her battles.
I think she does know.
Yeah, no, even Claire, I don't know.
Honestly, like, quite frankly,
I've been with you for, what, like,
a little bit over a month now.
Honestly, I'm not saying that to be polite,
but I'm just saying what I think here.
I think Claire, honestly, she's...
I don't know who her husband or partner is,
but he's very lucky, you know,
because the way she's able to remain calm,
you know, despite the sometimes tone of voice
I find completely inappropriate and things like that,
I do have a lot of admiration for this woman.
Honestly, like, some days, when she will expect the list,
I'm gonna also ask her the question,
"Claire, what is your secret?
What sort of short breath are you having?
There is a thing you do."
You need to tell me, there must be a secret.
No, really, it's unbelievable.
I mean, for me, it's a lesson of...
in self-control.
Not that I lack in the self-control,
but, you know, I've encountered very few people
able to remain calm under such circumstances.
Like, no, this is most unusual.
I think she deserved the Nobel Prize for Peace or something.
The Pro-Pace Keeping.
Yeah, and I think as well, like,
just when I started, there were a few other members of the team,
and I think they were all really quite difficult.
And I think Jason's, like, the only one left from that team,
so I think it actually used to be, like, a lot worse.
Oh, Jesus, really? What is that?
I don't know, it was just, like, a lot of strong opinions,
and people, like, when you did a bit of work,
people would, like, disagree a lot with the way you did it,
and there would be, like, a lot of debate
and a lot of chat about certain things.
But even, well, you know, having strong opinions
is not a problem, you know,
but they need to be backed by facts.
Like, you know, when I see him, like, downplaying the work,
the security teams and so on are doing,
I mean, this is not right, like, you know,
I mean, these people, they're doing what they can
at the end of the day, and they most likely have, you know,
some policies they have to stick to.
You see what I mean, like, in the book?
Yeah, security are rubbish, though.
Like, I do agree, like, the way he talks about them
isn't very nice, but they are very good.
Yeah.
And if you want to get to work with them,
if that ever happens, you will quite see.
Like, I do agree, like, they do have a job to do,
and obviously they've got their own stuff going on.
It's difficult for them, especially right now.
But, like, before when I worked with, like, one guy,
I would have, like, a meeting every two weeks or something like that,
and I pretty much, it was the same meeting every two weeks,
and I would tell them exact same things,
and he still, like, wouldn't understand what was going on.
I... well, these are most likely information security people.
Yeah.
It is difficult, but, like, again,
I don't deal with them that much anymore,
or something like that, but he just likes to go on a rant
about things like that.
This security thing is probably the biggest one, so...
Okay.
We'll get him some vodka or some whiskey.
He's gonna cool him down.
He doesn't drink, but yeah.
We'll find some tricks to get him to drink.
He'll become happy again.
Okay.
So, Zoe, yeah, so, as you were mentioning yesterday,
you spoke about an account that was used,
that was used, or that is used for the...
TerraFar automation on AWS.
And yesterday, when you were talking,
I think you went on to a repository
where there was a piece of code that was run by that user.
Am I correct?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Like, I can't remember...
Did we go over, like, the pipelines with you before?
We went briefly over the Azure DevOps pipeline.
Yeah.
Yeah, so, like, I can show you, like, so...
Just now we have, like, this pipeline, for example,
which is just an elastic search to me.
Like, it's just an AWS.
There's not a big, like, resource or anything like that.
But this works in Azure DevOps.
So, it must...
Where's the pipeline?
Yeah.
Like, it is, like, it can see that there's been changes
being made and stuff, so I'm pretty sure it works like as in...
I'm sure I've added at least IPs
and removed them for whatever reason, like, changed them.
So, yeah.
Like, are you...
Have you created, like, a branch or anything yet?
No, no, no, no. I mean, on the AWS side,
all I've done, all I did first of all was
trying to find any, you know,
users with the right privileges,
able to run some Terraform scripts.
I did find two with Terraform in them,
but they hadn't...
The...
Both hadn't been used in, like, a couple of years.
So, this is why I thought to myself,
maybe it is better to, you know, to set up a new one.
So, I created a new user with the name TerraformUser
with the right privileges in order to use that to, you know,
to design all the Terraform script for all the elements
we have on AWS at the moment.
And once tested and once I know it is,
at a minimum acceptable, I'll start to check them
to check them into the GitHub repository.
This is the plan ahead, really.
So, we do have this service account.
This is the old one.
So, I think that's the user that should have been used.
So, SCArk/Obs.
Okay, okay.
Okay, so, let me see.
If I can see that user there.
One second.
Sorry, my laptop is a little bit slow,
but it's going to start actually, so I'll have to update it.
Okay, where is the signing?
One second, I'm trying to, yeah, sign.
No, what is that?
Okay, I am using it.
Just putting my ID.
Next.
Alright, so make.
And press right.
So, just key in the password and it will be the,
the, yeah.
So, it is going to be 664, that sounds like a lot of things.
Okay.
So, when I go into IMUsers.
So, it's SC.Ark.
Okay.
So, SC.
Yeah, I can, let me share my screen and show you that user.
So, you should be able to see my screen now.
So, yeah, I got that user.
Okay, okay, this one here.
Yeah.
Because it is disabled console access.
Yeah, so, like, it has actually, like, it's been disabled.
We can't use it, but that was the account that was being used.
Yeah, and it doesn't have that.
So, I don't know what to do, to do the, should we, I don't know.
Take the.
Like, I think it would be fine just to use it again, but, so,
it might be better to, like, you move it to this new user that we have,
which is basically the same user with just the cloud version of the account.
Just to keep it consistent with everything else.
Because these accounts are being used to, like, run all our pipelines
and everything like that anyway.
So, great way to make sense to add it.
So, okay, so, in this case then, as these, I think this user is,
but it was used yesterday.
Yes, that's what I mean.
The pipelines probably run still, so.
Okay, so.
Because it's like an AD group, I guess, like, it doesn't care that what AD says about it,
but an AD is gone.
Okay, so, I'm not sure what to do here.
So, should I just try to change the policy for that very specific account?
I'll send you the name of this new user, right?
And if you want to create, like, the same account, or, like, the same permissions with an account with that name or whatever.
Okay.
Okay, I'll try to see if I can.
No, no, I don't think I'll be able to create another account with the same name
because I think the system will most likely refuse it because this one is already.
It's not the same name, it does have AC1 at the start.
Is there any somewhere though?
Ah, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
There is a one here, yeah.
Yeah, AC1.
Okay, okay, so let's do that then.
So, I'm gonna forget about the, I'll try to disable the account I created yesterday,
and I'm gonna create a new one with the right privileges and with that name.
And then if you add it, once you create, like, an access key, you can add it to Key Vault,
but maybe it would be better if we can just chat through that bit after you've done that if you want.
Okay, no problem, no problem, no problem, let's do that.
I'm gonna do that way, okay.
Okay, so, okay, so thank you very much for your time today.
No worries.
Enjoy your first day.
The day where we first did, so we're having beer and whiskey.
I had a few beers last night, so I've got to...
Ah, excellent, excellent, well done.
I had just some water yesterday, Jesus, like that.
Okay, so...
Sometimes you need a drink coming out of that call.
Sorry?
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Yeah, you will be fine.
Okay, so thank you very much.
You're welcome.
So thank you very much for your time today, and are you gonna be coming to the office on the 12th?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay.
So, do you think Claire will...
Do you think we can force Claire to go to the pub instead of the restaurant on the first day,
and I don't think it's appropriate for a new employee?
The only problem with going to the pub is there's no pubs around the office.
Ah, yeah, it's true.
It's true that it's only garages and...
Yeah, it's more difficult.
But we should arrange to go to the pub sometime.
Absolutely, absolutely. Ah, some whiskey at last.
We're running out of whiskey in sterling, you know.
Oh, really?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I finished all of it, yeah.
Stop by.
So let me know once you clear that up, Claire,
and we can go through the pain-tied part if you want.
Okay, no problem, no problem.
I'll do so.
It's not gonna take me long.
Just a few minutes, okay.
Okay, okay, sorry, thank you.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
[phone beeps]
[coughs]
[footsteps]
[indistinct]
[clears throat]
[ Inaudible Discussion ]