the Linux servers are actually doing and where they send the emails, whatever that is fine.
I know, I know, but if they want to have a discussion.
The operational emails, the reporting emails.
I know.
Colin did actually mention apparently there's some concern about customer data.
So there's no customer data coming out of those emails.
The only thing we had with customer data was that builds server which has gone now.
Yep. No, I don't know.
So like I was giving him that.
I was like fair enough. It's saying that every single is like opening up a huge section.
That's cool. I don't mind.
You can have a chat, but I was like, I was like, there's no, there's no network rules here.
This is basically, and it was like the question was, it was like, it's fine.
All I need is no network rules.
We're just using 365 as a really for Prisma Cloud and all I need is the Prisma Cloud email address
enabled again, to send like it used to.
And they're like, oh, that, like, would it work?
Like two factors needed for 365 emails.
No, not all of them.
You don't have to be.
We can make it.
So yeah, now I have to have the phone call about that.
So, yeah.
Yeah. So, I'm still going to be working on this.
So this is going to probably end up bigger than what Ross and that started out with.
And because we've got to look at the encryption stuff and I was having a chat
recalling about it this morning.
Apparently, what the what's the sort of?
Oh, sorry.
I know I just started waffling on about database users that automating database users when we're
creating the databases.
So like the, the, the, the database users is probably the simple bit, but there's obviously
certain databases have like encryption required.
So that will have to get tacked on somehow on top of it.
And then Colin, Colin's obviously wanting to review the actual accounts that are there
because there was some people that had like DBO to start off with.
The BI team, somebody created them, one after sales guys or somebody had created them at some
point, a data services reader and they were hooking directly from on-prem to
does your databases to pull data.
And obviously that's not supposed to be happening.
And isn't that, no, no, it's like, if they were doing it, they would be looking at a view
at the, at the most, but they weren't.
It was a user on the work on stuff directly from databases rather than a view.
So that I, they shouldn't have a reader.
So like God knows how that happened.
Yeah.
So I would need to, why don't we just turn on encryption for all the databases by default
anyway?
Well, see that, that might be where we go.
But obviously Colin is one.
That's what I'll very likely end up doing with, with replacement canary pastures.
We prove a concept of that with that, that BI replica cluster.
Yes.
That rest encryption.
I couldn't get TLS working.
I think now that it's been a few years, I could probably get that going.
Yeah.
So I saw obviously like Colin wants a bit more input around about the database.
Stuff, which is fine because that's don't have an issue with that.
Dave's.
So the plan for that after sales event store stuff is next Thursday night, Greg's on call.
So we'll leave it to Greg.
I'll do that.
I mean, it should just be a case of taking, stopping the nodes,
changing the config, turning the other three nodes, well, all the nodes back on,
and they should just all sync up.
I don't think there's any more complicated to that.
It should just work.
Might take a while for them to sync back up.
It should get there.
Yeah, 10 pages.
I might.
Yeah.
So I've estimated two hours on that.
So there'll be an outage window at night.
I don't even think, are you being holiday next week anyway?
I know.
It'll be more than two hours.
Possibly.
It'll be interesting.
And like you'll need to kick it off and just go to bed.
Basically, there's no point sitting around waiting for it.
It could take all night and into the day.
It's been that long since they were synced up.
Obviously, it was a lot quicker when I did it, but there's no guarantee of that.
Yeah.
Would it be easier dumping the data?
I don't think it would be any easier dumping the data.
But can you do that?
I don't know.
It's not a database.
So I don't know how it works.
Oh, no, it's a database.
So technically--
Oh, sorry.
It's not a database that I'm familiar with.
Oh, yeah.
It's not a SQL database.
I can't run my SQL dump against it.
No, no, you can't do that.
So I think I would just stand the back up and let them sync up.
It's not really a database though, anyway.
Sort.
Well, sorry.
Sorry, not by--
So I will do that.
You've got your stuff that you're doing.
You're picking up stuff and sorting yourself out.
Yeah, just--
Adding stuff as I go to.
Keith, you're still doing the ECM stuff.
How much have you got with it?
Like, how are you getting on with it?
Oh, it's going on ground.
I think there's much left of the initial config.
Cool.
Yeah, the bigger bits, the setting up, the apps in that.
And I found out talking to the Red yesterday,
apparently the code for the image core and scale that's in GitHub
is not what's running in production.
Because last time he tried to make a change,
Craig couldn't get it to work, which was like three or four years ago.
That was the Java thing that I was thinking of
when I thought that they were trying to run
AdCenter or something while Linux and got stuck.
I think it was--
Red had just made a change to the image crawler or scaler,
and they couldn't get it working.
Yeah, but there's that there.
And so, yeah, the work in there is that the stuff that's in the ECM
and image fintech repo needs to get the same treatment
as what I've done to web builder, stop builder, AdCenter feeds,
and that move them to DevOps pipelines for each,
like one for the scaler, one for the crawler,
and then probably one for the various scripts.
Or I kind of talked to Keith about this,
like maybe batching up related scripts,
unless they're all related and watch the case,
they all just get released together
because there's not really a built process there.
It's just really deploying.
And also, the assets, the JavaScript and the PHP stuff,
so they can all be deployed by pipeline
and work in a similar way to what I'm doing with the AC.com stuff.
So virtual machine and basically more config,
which Keith's sort of tying off at the moment.
And then there's application config,
which I'm saying with the same inverted quotes,
which would be like any kind of web config,
a web server config, any secrets.
And config files for the Java tasks in particular,
that will come out of the Ansible AC.com repo,
like all the other stuff is.
And then the AC image feeds repo will then be like,
that's the apps that are being deployed.
So yeah, very much just try and mimic what I've started doing with AC.com anyway.
So there is a bit of work left there.
Cool, should we write this down?
Should I write this in this ticket?
Because that was a brain that are like,
do you want to write it in that ticket?
Because you just spat out a whole load of things.
I suppose I could do something.
Yeah.
I've talked to Keith about it, so.
Cool.
Okay.
Right, so I've still got that.
So that's at least another two weeks worth of work anyway.
Marcel, I tried to split up those tickets.
So what I did was I renamed the old ticket
to terraforming the AWS VPC.
See this, how you already had a branch that had that code on it.
I created another one that was basically just like a starting ticket.
Yeah.
For you to just capture like, so obviously VPCs, EC2s,
and like anything else that we need to capture.
So if we just get a list in that ticket,
we can close that one off and then I'll create new tickets
based on the resources so that we can split the mail into tickets
and create PRs for each individual bits for the AWS stuff.
And then that means that we know exactly which bits
that we've still got left to do in that
and make them smaller tickets.
Instead of just going like terraforming all of AWS.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I don't want to repeat that.
Which was, yeah, yeah.
So once you've tidied up the branch that you've got,
we can get a PR and have a wee look through it
and see if we want to tidy up anything before we merge it,
which would be cool.
So you've still got some stuff there.
And Zoe, you're doing the clusters, Prisma, Cloud,
you can't really go any further on now.
Because emails.
So you've been...
There's some other conflict to look up.
Yeah.
I don't know, I could probably get a small ticket.
Well, I think for the next two weeks,
so there's obviously, I think, what there were certain...
Because I've only got next week and then I'm on holiday for two weeks.
Yes, so, yeah.
Well, we can see what comes in then.
What I was going to say was there's obviously these new,
really golden signal things.
Oh, yeah, okay.
So I would just start picking these up
and just see how they would apply to the,
to, I guess, the example app.
I mean, we've already got some of these things in place.
It's just how we pull that out into a module that the devs can use
for their apps, just to make sure that everything's monitored.
So I guess that would be the next one.
And then...
Okay, cool.
That would sort you for a week.
And then, I guess, at some point, we get to look at
the Zero Trust in Kubernetes sort of stuff.
Oh, yeah.
But we'll have a bigger discussion about that as a group
and just see where we think we're going with that as well.
I don't remember that director's thing.
Ignore that for now.
I had a chat with Ross.
So he didn't realize it was paid for.
So when I had a chat about that,
he's just going to keep it in a database now.
He's going to just stitch the director's stuff.
So it's not free?
No, no.
So it's like, it was free for...
It was direct us, wasn't it?
Direct us.
Because he was like,
the self-hosted one's completely free.
I was like, it's completely free.
Because he hadn't clicked in this tab.
So it was completely free for up to $5 million.
And you're like, well, we go over that.
So we'd have to pay.
So I was like, this might not actually be that expensive.
And I was like, in the cloud version, it's like $99 a month.
It's really not that bad.
I was like, all you need to do is just get them to give you a price.
And then right up a proposal of what you're putting in it
and how much it costs.
And I'm sure somebody will say, oh, he's like, I can't even do that.
I can't even do that.
I'm like, I'm expecting it.
I'm like, you do, you do.
So if he doesn't want to do it,
and he just wants to stick it in the data, he's that same.
And then, but yeah, we would have had to pay for it.
And somebody would have had to sign off.
And even getting this, somebody would have had to sign off.
And then I'm like, yeah.
Because it had just been like, I even the data in it,
it's like three of our names and like being able to manage,
to patch management and updates and stuff
so that they could keep track of it.
But I mean, he can do that in a database.
He just wanted the UI.
He says, so.
So that's, I don't, so I think in that case,
I don't think there's really much else.
Everybody's got stuff.
Yeah, Jason, you can, you can decide with Greg,
what Greg does when he comes back,
which servers that he should pick up if he's,
if he can remember what it was that you had a discussion about.
And we'll start getting him doing some migrations,
to go on to as well.
If it's the Galeric clusters, then cool.
That's probably a good one.
He's got quite a bit of experience with that,
I'm sure do love going back to them.
But it's what makes sense.
It's what I know is how they hang together.
Yeah, yeah, I think I probably need to be involved
with some bits anyway, but.
Yeah, but you do like to be involved with all of them, Jason.
Sorry, what?
I said, you do like being involved with all of them,
and to be in the big switch.
Well, no, it's just, I mean, obviously,
I'm not very good at writing things down.
And like just much, just recently in the last couple of weeks,
I've been doing a lot of work that's directly related
to the Galeric clusters with the character set stuff
and shit like that.
And then also remembering that I wanted to do things like TLS
and that, which was tricky, which I couldn't get
to work the first time around.
So like, yeah, I want to try and set that stuff up as well.
But yeah, that's also just, it's like, particularly with things
like the ATO proxies and the Galeric clusters.
But yeah, could get them to do the images service,
because really that just rails servers.
Yeah.
Get those done.
Possibly the big cash servers as well,
since AC images being done.
Can do the big cash and stuff.
I keep all the other stuff together.
Yeah.
Or they could be keys next targets.
True, true, unless he wants to break from images.
I would get to know how it all hands together
though at the same time.
Yeah.
So two through five, I think of the images to servers.
I think that just rails apps servers.
So that'd be easy.
That'd just be cooking kind of what I've done with AC.com.
Images one, a prod images one,
my real images one.
That's like, I think they're basically just serving images.
And then the Vcaches are caching images from AC image to serve up.
So that'd be like three separate sort of migration jobs, I think.
That's like, I don't think.
Nope.
Yeah.
So that's like, I.
But yes, I do like to be involved.
It's like, the only person, I mean, I'm the only person left
that has enough knowledge about our Linux systems
and where we're sort of planning to go with it.
I will, will the bits and pieces,
it's like all the historic bits and pieces that just, I, it's like,
at all.
Since JL left, I've been able to just figure out so much more of it.
Yeah.
It was quite a block working with Craig and JL on retrospect.
I was not able to really learn enough because they had the
rigid ways of wanting to do things which I didn't always agree with.
And I know you've done that in them.
Well, yeah, I mean, anyone's way of doing it, someone's going to
disagree with for sure.
And I'll disagree with my own work when I look back on it, I'm sure.
There's no even at those.
But it's also just like, you know, they've got to be interesting workers,
well, so I never had a chance to really learn much.
So since, yeah, since JL's left, it's just been like, oh cool,
well, this shit's easy.
There's nothing to worry about.
It's all simple.
Why did we make it so, why did everything have to be such a bit
complicated mess to those guys?
Yeah, I think it's the same.
It's always the same.
But it's like, you always worry.
It's like, because we've had that previously, people leave you like, oh my
God, how are we going to do this?
And you're like, no, it's fine.
Yeah, yeah.
And then you learn stuff.
You learn stuff.
That's cool.
And I've seen that from the outside.
Whenever like Craig and JL left and go, oh my God, that's fine.
We're pretty skilled people.
We're pretty good at figuring shit out.
We'll be fine.
Yeah, no, it was always fine.
It's always fine.
We always adapt and learn and we get better for it.
That's just cool.
So it's all good.
Cool.
Okay.
Right.
Go, go do things.
Go be happy.
Almost lunchtime.
Get a cup of tea.
That Halo Tenders bullshit should be working now.
Oh yeah, I did notice that.
I don't know what it was.
I haven't gone back to them all over anything, but I just closed it and put
them out saying that it's been opened up.
I could see in the proxy it's been on green.
So a student's working.
Anything that's not working on those servers I don't really care about.
Yeah, it's like I knew this was broken and I left it because no one asked for it.
There was a symbol.
It was just because for whatever reason that's been deployed to the 10-150-233 network,
which the 232 and 233 networks were open to each other previously,
but a firewall has been put in front of the 232 network and we just
hadn't had a request to open those particular servers up.
Yep.
Aye.
So aye.
I knew it was broken.
Didn't care because Dumbledore didn't ask about it.
Previously, no one had told us to open it back up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
I don't even know if he'd had permission to get it open back up.
Well, technically it was never down.
No.
Yeah, it was not down.
It was just that because they put this firewall in which broke everything immediately.
And that was one of the bits where I was like,
"Ah, tell me, you're going to do this stuff.
You've just cut off like AC.com from everything."
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's fine.
Oh, aye.
That's cool.
Yes.
No, that's it.
Everyone else can go.
I was like, "Everyone else can go."
That's fine.
Yeah, no, that's sad.
I don't think I'm getting a house.
Yeah, cool.
And yes, I will catch you all later, I guess.
Yeah, catch you later.
Go to it, does that?
Short and sweet.
Right, go.
Bye.
[BLANK_AUDIO]