I mean I'm dealing with a lot of the like basically upgrading all the legs to stuff.
That's been putting my lab so that's what I've been working on.
Jason's looking at upgrading from getting off of Centos because Centos has gone into life this year.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So we're looking to move to Ubuntu.
It's always doing Azure stuff and honestly I don't know what Claire's got planned so you know she might say
ignore Event Store and look at this instead.
Okay, alright.
So basically we have from my understanding you tell me if I'm wrong but beyond the areas to which every single of us is assigned
there is also a lot of research work so to speak. Am I correct?
Um, I don't know. It's hard to do research on these legacy apps where even the developers like inherited it so nobody knows some stuff but
I mean, the estates are big. There's a lot of stuff going on.
Yeah, you know for the most part you're only going to be looking at small portions at any one time.
Alright, okay.
So yeah, I mean I wouldn't stress too much. Get to know the company, go through all the learning stuff all the videos.
I mean it's boring but there's stuff like the fire stuff that they want you to do for insurance purposes.
Alright, okay, okay, okay.
Honestly don't stress too much about like not having too much to do.
There's a lot to do. There's a lot in the backlog. I don't even know how to see the backlog.
There's a whole bunch of stuff that's in this sprint. So there's a lot to do.
Alright, okay, okay.
So a whole bunch of stuff that will eventually get done. So if you want to take and have a look through that, I don't think there's going to be much.
I can see SFTP pentesting, finding, review recommendation, security banner.
Yeah, so there's a bunch of stuff that we set up. We've got some FTP servers that apparently some other car manufacturers want to use.
Again, we set it up and the day-to-day running, we don't involve.
Okay, alright, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, application gateway, cleanup, all projects.
Okay, I see. At least with the backlog, I see where I go.
Have you got a link to the Gira?
I'm not sure.
So you've got the first one is the support one.
Yeah, yeah.
Second one is like the project board.
Okay.
I think, what else?
Have you got an experience with the Gira?
No, no, no, no, I was mostly working on with AWS and Google Cloud.
But right before starting this neuro, I started to take some courses on Azure.
So right now on Azure, really, I can, as I was telling you, I can fairly easily get some because I've heard that the company is mostly right now.
The company is mostly writing an application with .NET, am I correct?
I know there is some rabion.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
So basically, what I've been working, I've been doing two things basically.
So right now, if someone is giving some source code on whichever application it is, I can easily take that, you know, get the Docker file, build the container, push the container into the Azure.
You know, container registry and use that to deploy on Kubernetes.
That is all clear now.
And I'm also trying to get to complete a course on administration, like system administration in Azure.
Yeah.
So this is one point.
I mean, I don't think we actually build the containers to build up.
That's the dev team that do it.
Okay.
So we look after the health of the Kubernetes cluster and we don't flag any issues that might come up.
All right.
The actual containers themselves.
We don't build them.
All right.
Okay.
But we are expected to publish it.
If things go wrong, it's a strange term, because, yeah, so really we look after the architecture.
Okay.
So not all the infrastructure, not so much the, like, the workings of the containers or anything like that.
And in terms of the architecture, this is just another question for my previous roles.
I was mostly working in DevOps team.
And in my two previous roles, the DevOps team was in charge of finding ways to minimize the cost of running.
Yeah.
Is it also part of our traditions or is it?
The unique thing with the AnnoClock is that we actually have like two and a half purpose-built data centers.
So the AnnoClock likes to do everything internally.
Yeah.
So for the longest time, I say that I've only been here a year, but the story is that they like to do everything internally.
We've already got these data centers and all this hardware that they've paid for.
Yeah.
So there's no rush to run into the cloud and basically pay again.
Okay.
So we've got some stuff in the cloud and we've got a lot that's still on premise.
And so we're a proper hybrid company.
All right.
Okay.
I see.
The aim, the aim soon though is to have all of our traffic going through Azure as the first point.
Okay.
So all the traffic will go to Azure and then if it needs to come to something internal,
we'll just come down one of the express routes that we've got.
So that switchover will probably happen next year or something.
All right.
I mean, that doesn't really change much for us.
It's just going to have to be aware of where the traffic is coming from.
Okay.
So I'll have just one other question.
You see the, when you were going through the backlog just earlier, I saw there was one
task where it was written, what was about dealing with some SFTP server that because of some
pain testing, I think, yeah, that happened on that.
So, I haven't opened that.
Well, I haven't, obviously it is important to open that ticket and see what it is saying.
But just like that, I haven't opened the ticket here, ticket here.
If I were to maybe access the backlog and go on that SFTP server, the first question
I'll have to ask you is, do you think this SFTP server is running on-prem on the Linux
box or do you think it's more Windows box from your experience?
It'll be on-prem.
It'll be a Linux box.
Yeah.
All right.
So, to solve that issue, for example, if I were, for example, to log into that SFTP server,
just trying to find out how it is set up.
So, maybe checking which ports are open, checking if it is updated regularly and trying to see
if maybe there is a possibility to implement some security measures for that specific box.
Do you think this is what is expected from us if we were to deal with that ticket?
This is my question.
No, I mean, we, it's set up.
The PEN test will have its recommendations, which are actually pasted in the ticket.
Our Sinclair will update it when we move it into the live queue.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah, so if you do do the ticket and you have a look and you see the recommendations
and then obviously you make the changes that are required, but if you do have any other
suggestions, yeah, just raise them in the, you either raise them in the ArcOps channel
or during our stand-up at the end of the day and all that, chat about it, or something,
if you think it needs more than like a five, ten minute talk, you can always just like
arrange a call and you can all just hop on a call and discuss it.
Okay, okay, all right.
Okay, okay.
Now, I understand better when you're saying that we are the ones dealing with the architect
word D. Yeah, I understand better.
Okay, okay.
Yeah.
I think there might be, I mean, we know that there's some things like you've got a couple
of users who for whatever reason refuse to use keys, so they're using a user name and
password.
I mean, no, that's not recommended to them.
Apparently the manufacturer is being adamant.
And so this is like the only way that they can move the stuff.
Okay, okay.
I mean, if they, I mean, out of the blue just like that, if this is what they're doing,
you know, maybe, you know, we can ask them to confirm whether the connection is maybe
always coming from the, I don't know, I don't know yet, but I will ask them to find out
from where the connection is coming.
Is it coming from one of their own servers or is it one of the employees trying to connect?
I mean, trying to understand and maybe from that, from that, if I were to delegate that
ticket, my suggestion maybe would be to try to see if we are sure, for example, that the
connections are all the time coming from the UK or from a specific region.
Maybe one security measure we can put in place is, you know, trying to see if we can implement
some IP tables that would allow specifically these IP addresses and nothing else.
And obviously, prior to implement these IP tables, trying to see if we can write maybe
a batch script that will make sure that the necessary ports are always accessible just
in case.
Yeah, this is one suggestion.
We've got like proper firewalls.
We rarely have to do things at a server level.
All right.
Okay.
I mean, I would hope that it's locked down the specific IPs, but I don't know.
I mean, we, a lot of times, they'll ask for stuff to be set up and we'll give recommendations,
but the company doesn't always listen.
All right.
Okay.
Yeah.
I mean, really, really, that was, you know, that was, you know, what you showed us, what
you showed me and what you told me that was really, really useful because now I have a
better idea on, you know, the sort of works.
So basically, is it right for me to assume that I would say 70 to 80% of the tasks we're
dealing with are coming from this backlog channel?
Yeah.
I mean, once we are filing, that's when like clear all this stuff out.
So if you're setting with three or four things still to do, she's not going to throw more
stuff at you unless it's urgent.
So for the most part, you're only going to have a few things to do every two weeks.
Okay.
All right.
I mean, a lot of the things are not quick.
So a lot of things take turns.
Okay.
All right.
So you told me you've been with our network for about a year.
Yeah, last October.
Oh, that's great.
And what is the thing you did for, what was the, what did you find the most difficult to
cope with in terms of the work we're doing?
Yeah.
What I mean, for example, for example, in my, in my previous role in France, you know,
basically the, the aim was to help normal path group to become, you know, you know, ISO
2701 compliant.
And, and, and to be frank, you know, surely you've heard about the French culture.
You know, change is not, you know, the, the acceptance and management of change is not
the strength of.
I've only been to San Marlowe.
So I've not been.
San Marlowe.
Okay.
But, but, but to be honest with you, the, the, the, the France as a country and my fellow
French, my fellow French, you know, you know, they tend to be very resistant to change.
So the biggest issue I had in that role was actually, and believe it or not, was actually
trying to convince the, the, the board of the, I mean, the senior managers to even accept
the idea to become GDPR compliant.
It is a requirement by law for them to do that above all since a lot of French companies
did suffer some massive data security breaches, but still, still they, they will see it as
some, some sort of, you know, they will be very annoyed to comply with the law.
It's unbelievable that that was the most difficult part in, in the job release.
So, so whenever you need to start, when you start, starting the audit was, was very difficult,
you know, implementing the, the, the conclusion from the audit was even more difficult.
So the difficulty really was trying to convince them every day to, to, to move along with the
thing.
So, so my question was actually in the same direction.
What is the most challenging part, I would say, of, of the day to day task we, we have
to accomplish because I can already see one thing I can already see is,
I don't know.
I mean, it's, it's pretty, just dealing with legacy apps is probably my biggest thing because
no one knows anything about them.
No one knows how, how the intricate details of how they work.
Okay.
I mean, I mean, I think that that's just unique to the issue.
But otherwise, I mean, I still don't really know, like Terraform, like I've edited Terraform.
But when I get to the point of writing in Ansible and Terraform for these, the new AdCenter
servers, that's going to be like my first real dive in the writing Terraform from scratch.
Okay.
I'm still learning.
Oh, right.
So I came from AWS myself.
Okay.
And puppet.
So not even Ansible.
So it's been, yeah, getting to learn technologies.
I mean, there's way of being remote, but previously I was like on my own, like the only IT guy
in the company.
Oh, a lot of stress.
Yeah, the last few jobs.
Yeah.
But that's not true.
Before here, I left, come pick up, EEC and a Clelf.
Because I was on my own, I wanted to be part of a team.
And I joined Enable.
Do you know Enable?
They used to be SolarWinds.
SolarWinds, yeah, not SolarWinds.
Yeah.
And so with me and then the rest of the team were all in Belarus.
Oh.
So I joined them and I was like, okay, great.
I'll get to be part of a team again.
We'll be about chat and everything.
And obviously, like the language barrier was just too much.
I see.
So after six months, I was like, you know, I think this is working out.
So that's why I'm.
I see.
This is not.
I'm just happy being part of a team again.
I'm having people chat every day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, they were about sighted me as a people.
Yeah.
I see.
And in terms of the learning, Claire told me that we have, I think, subscriptions to O'Reilly.
Yeah.
I think I don't know what you'll be able to send those details out.
I don't know if I've actually got an O'Reilly login.
Oh, so you'll get a login for it.
Okay.
All right.
And how did you find, how did you find the, how did you find the, the learning with O'Reilly
so far?
Because I, me personally, I started looking at it.
Like, I came from AWS.
So I've worked for the zero a little bit.
So I was trying to go through all, honestly, I've sort of stopped.
I've been looking at it for a long time.
I don't know. I think it's just
the cost.
You can see here.
This is just one of the sites.
I don't know what the other
Jason will tell you.
1-6, the East South Street,
or Cabela and so on.
As you can see we've got 2.2 THz free
of CPU
12TB free.
I don't understand why we've got so much.
We've got 179TB free
of storage.
We've got loads of
CPU.
We've got another one of these as well.
Server side was the
I forgot which one's the newer one.
Oh Jesus.
What?
Yeah.
We've put all this money
in time into these data centers.
That's why there's no rush
to move to the cloud.
Yeah.
People go to the cloud because
you know
if you're starting a company
there's no way you would do all this now.
Yeah.
They've already got it in place.
So again 1.7THz
9.89TB
is free of memory
and 138TB is free of storage.
There's a bunch of, we're running
old bunch of stuff that
we're probably never actually have to look at.
There is a focus on being
cloudy when we can.
At the end of the day
we don't have to be.
We could just
pull back in and run everything locally.
I think for
redundancy states
being in a cloud data center
is better.
I think back in the day
or years ago
it was less reliable
like your own data center
especially the ones I know
got a bill.
I don't know why they're in
Zooer for Kubernetes. I'm guessing just because it's easier to manage.
Like the cost
of having someone come in and manage a whole Kubernetes cluster
when you can get Microsoft
to do it for you as part of the cost.
All right, I see.
When you are given a ticket
to deal with an application
and
when you don't find the documentation
who do you talk to in order to at least
have an idea
on how it works
and is it more to the
developers or
is there a...
Yeah, so the developers are
splitting the different teams. It's like the web team
I don't know
what we want to pull up.
But I know there's a few teams. There's like the one vehicle team
there's the web team
I think those are the only really two teams that we have to speak
to day to day.
So those
if I needed to know the ins and outs
I'd speak to them. But a lot of the time
if it's the newer stuff
then that's all going to be documented with the new get repo.
The other stuff
they just don't know.
They're just like, what else?
They have to go in the new stuff and look at the config files
and try and get a general gist
as to how it's operating.
I mean, look at AdSense
for instance, it's just a single jar that runs
so it's not
it's not going to be difficult to move
it's just going to be testing
testing it to make sure it all works as expected
because it's on an engine jam version as well
so I'm going to have to try and pull that up
so we might need to get the devs to make some tweaks
to the code
we'll see
Don't stress out, you've got nothing
you have nothing to do. It's going to be a very
very soft launch
I mean, it took me
like eight months before
I even started having to go on call
so
I don't think you have to worry about it too much
Okay, alright, okay
Really, thank you
thank you so much Greg
for taking the time to...
I mean, you should be able to call anyone on the team
or at least ask anyone on the team
and be like, got questions about this or that
Yeah, no problem
Adjacent comes off as like
rash and
like opinionated
and he is
he's got his opinion as to when
or how things should be done
so if you believe strongly in
differently
you have to fight your corner
Yeah, no problem
No problem
You've probably seen from our stand-ups
that we'd like to have a good complaint
sometimes
on what's going on in the company
I noticed
It's been
very chilled
which is different from where it was previously
where the sprints were
hard deadlines
and I had to
go on with it
Yeah, yeah
The only thing
I did find
I did
I found
a bit... well
I have some slight regrets around
is the fact that, you know
the laptop I have
I mean, when I was asked if I wanted
a Mac or Windows
obviously, I told them
okay, I'm gonna go for a Windows
with the idea
of installing maybe Red Hat
or Debian or something like that on it, right?
But then, to access the
Oh, no, yeah, you have to
go with our prints
Yeah, yeah, yeah
But yeah, I mean
I don't know if it's too late to change
but, yeah, speak to Claire
Yeah, I spoke to Claire because
the Windows is not is
you know
Yeah, I didn't know if you're like
"Oh, have they set this up on the Windows?"
I thought, "I have no idea"
I was from a Mac, so I'll act
I use it
Okay, yeah
I've never, to be frank
with you, for most of my
for the past decade or so
I've been mostly using
Linux laptops for work
but I know Linux and Mac are obviously
very close to each other
and Mac at least is stable
because the Microsoft laptop
I have is already crashing
and it's so sad, it's such a powerful machine
like, can you believe it? 64GB
64GB of RAM
and
You've got 64GB of RAM in yours
I have 64GB of RAM
on my laptop and 16 cores
can you believe it?
In the tell that they just gave you
Yeah, yeah, 64GB of RAM
I've got
I've got 16GB and
6 cores, i7
and Mac and Mac
and Mac is only like
I mean, this is a server, I was talking to
my colleagues, well, I was bragging
basically, I was talking to
one of my former colleagues and I said
he asked me, he said, "Hey, so Marcel, how are things
going in the UK?" I said, "It's great, you know
I'm working for this amazing
company, guess what, I've got a laptop
with 64GB of RAM" He said, "What?"
He said, "Maybe I should apply" I said, "Well, try
try it"
but he was also very
he was, I mean, I found that very impressive
and I checked, the laptop is worth
something like 7000 pounds
which is, Jesus
so, you know, yeah, so
because of that, you know, when I finish work
I keep it, why I keep my money
literally because you know, I cannot
I cannot afford to
Why you keep money on you?
You can't even make a bank account, you only keep cash
anymore? No, no, I still keep
just a little bit, you know, not too much
like 200 or 300 pounds just in case
you never know, so I keep
the laptop, yeah
Me, you know, maybe I'm a bit old school
in that regard but
there were a few times in my life
where the
I had issues with the car and so on
so, since then I thought to myself, okay
I just like
you, I don't use cash to pay
but I always keep
just a little amount, you know, somewhere
just in case, you know, just in case
the card is failing or, you know, God knows
what could be happening
so I just keep, so I keep the laptop right there
but it's a, yeah, it's a
it's a very powerful machine, this is a server
in fact, yeah, it's really sad
it is running Windows because
God knows what you could do with that
Linux or even Mac for that matter
but, well, that's another debate
okay, so Greg really, thank you
very much for your time this morning
thank you very much for helping me
to have a better
understanding of that
Yeah, that was pretty easy
and just, you'll be doing videos
and all that
I don't remember what I was doing
for the first couple of weeks
it's just a lot of reading
and creating videos
yeah, I think I have
a call with Jason to go over the infrastructure
and that, so I don't know if Claire's
going to arrange that as well
yeah, if you have
such a call with Jason
if obviously, if the two of you don't mind
I wouldn't mind joining just to, you know, to listen in
and see...
I've been talking about like a year ago when I started
I had a call with Jason to cover infrastructure
ah, okay, okay, okay
yeah, in this case, yeah
because she said that when she will be back
tomorrow
we will have
a call with Jason
to talk about the infrastructure
she did mention that
I mean, I imagine it'll be with Jason
because I've been here a year
but there's still stuff that I don't know
stuff that I find out
in like abbreviations
that, you know
you're just like, okay, that's what that stands for
but yeah, you'll learn something
every day, at least
yeah, yeah, yeah
because we did
okay
okay, so really
Greg, thank you very much for your time
and obviously, if I have
some other questions
then you just compliment
I'll write you a message on
so I've probably got plans for lunch today
for lunch today
I don't know, maybe I'm just going to have
some salad because I'm trying to lose weight
a bit, you know, you wouldn't believe it
but I am 110 kilograms
well, I've got your beat on that
oh, really?
I think
I have around 112
I'm aiming to get down to like
80 or something like that
I have the same issue because
I have some of my family members calling me an elephant
so, you know
it's not nice from them but that's what they're doing
so
and obviously
in my family, we have
a lot of people
have suffered and did suffer from
high blood pressure
and things like that so I need to be
careful so that's why I want to
try to lose a bit of weight
that's a very good question
so I'll tell
I don't know where it is
I mean in terms of who has the best Jalof
in West Africa
Ghana and Nigeria
are always fighting over who has the best Jalof
I wonder
is Ivory Coast sitting there
thinking well, they're both wrong
in that specific regard
some Maivurian people
would tell you that the Ivory Coast
is the best in terms of Jalof
but to be frank
it's not true
Nigeria
and Senegal
regarding that specific
and that I think they are most likely the best
but
the Ivory Coast has some other
specialities
that are also very famous
there is one we call
Aloko
I don't know
maybe
if
providing you can eat anything
I can try to see if I can maybe
arrange the next time
we go into the office
maybe I can try to bring some and you will try
and you will see
Aloko
is basically
fried plantains
but it is done in a way
that it is
I've tried that with
some Japanese friends
Russian friends, British friends and so on
they've all liked it very much
and I believe this is the
specialty of the Ivory Coast
but regarding the Jalof
the Ivoryans would brag about being the best
but they are not
I think Senegal and Nigeria are the best from far
not Ghana
to be honest
I don't think so
I truly believe
the one from Nigeria
and Senegal are the best
from very far
but
I'm not saying the one from Ghana is not good
this is not what I'm saying
but
the Nigerian Senegal are
a bit outclassing everyone else
but
I wouldn't say that loudly in front of
some of my foreign people
they might curse me
for that if I were to say that in front of some of my foreign people
but the truth is
this is the truth to be frank
ok thank you very much for your time
sit in the car
no problem thank you very much Gregg
thank you a lot
you too, thank you
you
(air whooshing)
(slurping)